All right. Uh, can you guys hear me? Put
a one in the chat. Good evening,
everyone. Um, it is good to be with you
all tonight.
Um, I see you guys have been uh waiting
and y'all look like y'all are excited
and ready to go. So, again, just put a
one in the chat if you could hear me
well.
Um, all right. All I needed to see was
one one. Excellent. Excellent.
Excellent. All right, guys. So, um, we
have,
uh, something pretty significant to to
talk about tonight, and I'm going to
jump right in. We're not going to be on
for long.
Um, but there are some pretty
significant things that need to be
shared. So, we're going to have a word
of prayer. You guys, uh, share this
link, let people know that we are live.
Uh, tell them to tune in.
Um, I have a
message
for for us today. This is this is for
us. This is for 7th Day Adventist. And
this is an appeal. Once again, it's an
appeal.
Um, so let me jump in. Let's pray. Let's
get to this. I got some a couple of
videos that I need to show you. Uh, and
uh, we're going to talk about some
pretty important things. So, let's pray.
Heavenly
Father, Lord, I ask that you would
please speak, Lord, to your people
tonight, Lord. Um, speak as you have
been speaking, Lord. Your voice has
never changed. Your word has never
changed. Um, Lord, help us to trust your
word. Help us to obey your word. And we
thank you for hearing and answering
because we ask it in Jesus name. Amen.
Amen.
Okay guys, so
um we need to talk a little bit about
project 2025 tonight. And um what I want
to say is is first of all
um
our I praise God I praise God
for being
introduced to this Adventist message.
Um, I think back to that night when
um our friend
D introduced us to Daniel chapter 7,
Babylon, Midapers, Greece,
Rome. I remember that night, all of us
in the house,
um, smoking
marijuana, doing our
thing, having a conversation about the
new world order, of which we knew
nothing
about. And then Dwight, a friend of a
friend of ours, began asking us, "What
day do we think the Sabbath is on?" And
we thought it was such a weird and
off-the-wall and crazy
question. And that has to be the most
important night in my
life with without a shadow of a doubt.
And what I learned back then in
1994 1993 what I learned back then in
um has so gripped me
uh that it changed everything. So, y'all
know left the music industry, left
everything, me and my brother who who's
now passed. Um, but left
everything and followed this message
because we believed it with all of our
heart. And I still believe it with all
of my
heart. And to see the things that have
been unfolding over the last
uh the last decade easily
um has just been
mind-blowing. But it has been confusing
to
me, genuinely confusing to
me
how we are where we
are and we're not making more noise than
we're making right now.
The things we have prophesied, the
things we have been warning for
over 150 years at
least. How is it that those things are
right up on us right now and many of us
are in
denial? I'm going to be honest with you
guys.
Um, you know, I've always considered
like, you know, what I would call in my
own understanding the liberal Adventist.
And what I mean by liberal Adventist
would be the kind of person that I
thought, you know, they're not even
studying their Bible. They're like,
"Yeah, this is fine and drinking alcohol
is fine and you know all." So, I've
always kind of been like, "Yeah, you
know, the li the liberal adventist who
is just like, hey, whatever I think is
right is right." Um, is going to be the
greatest threat to the Adventist
church. But seeing what has happened
within within so-called conservative
circles is really pretty scary,
y'all. It is really pretty
scary because there is almost near
silence when it comes to the threat of
Christian nationalism.
It's almost like we're not going to talk
bad about our team. Since when did we
become teammates with Christian
nationalism? Don't understand
it. Um, but I'm going to put that on
pause for a second and I need to show
you all something. I need to show you
all something. So you'll remember um you
know our current president said some
time back that he had no idea about
project 2025 what it was who the people
were etc. And you know I I saw many
adventists like really yeah see now it
really doesn't matter. I've always said
this you guys.
It's prophecy is not about one person,
right? The issue in these prophetic
times is not about the president. It is
about a movement. It is about a movement
that we were told would seek to hijack
political power for their
benefit. Put a one in the chat if that
makes sense to you.
We have
prophesied that a religious power would
seek to hijack political power in the
name of
Jesus in order to bring about the very
things that prophecy has foretold.
So Adventists should have never gotten
caught up in, well, we're going to
defend this party versus this party
because all we were looking for was,
well, who who is apo what power is
apostate Protestantism going to seek to
latch on
to in order to fulfill prophecy?
It should not have mattered to us if
they latched on to the Democratic party
or an independent party or the
Republican party. All we should have
been looking for was was well who are
they going to latch on to? No need to
defend. No need to no no not them. All
we need to do is plainly and clearly
just step back and see okay who is
apostate Protestantism? What political
arm are they going to attempt to
hijack, to
infiltrate so that they can get laws
passed? to have to
explain
to Bible believing
Adventists what is clearly visible to
the
eye. What everybody else in America is
seeing and warning against. atheists
warning against other
Christians who don't believe as we
believe but who clearly see what's going
on warning against. And
yet we have Adventists who are still
saying, "Well, maybe the Sunday law can
be passed by the godless people.
Maybe the Sunday law can be passed
by by climate change and things of this
nature. So, you remember I know nothing
about project 2025, but let's go to the
screen and I want you to just uh check
out this article. Um, here we go.
Um, this is from
Politico
and here is Paul Dans, the ousted
director of Project
2025,
saying he's
delighted that Trump is implementing his
agenda after
all. There you see the web the the the
the website
uh
address beyond my wildest dreams the
architect of project 2025 is ready for
his victory lap. Now some of you may
have seen this already and that's not
even what I'm talking about. I mean it
is what I'm talking about but this is
not the main thing. What I want to show
you
um see if uh this
will All right. Give me one
second.
Okay, so here we
go. Economic Policy
Institute. By the way, if you guys want
these slides, I will make them
available. And they're not many. They're
not many. Uh it's not a it's not a long
presentation tonight, but I have a lot
to say. Um but I'm gonna try to say it
in a short
time. Nominating Jonathan Barry as
solicitor of labor. President Trump
nominated Jonathan Barry as a solicitor
of labor at the Department of Labor, DO.
If
confirmed, Barry will be the chief legal
officer at DO and have the independent
authority to initiate laws to enforce
more than 180 federal labor laws,
including the Fair Labor Standard Act
and Occupational Safety and Health Act.
Barry is currently a managing partner at
Bdon Gray and Associates PLLC.
Previously, listen to this now.
Previously, Barry served as the acting
assistant secretary for policy at the
Department of Labor during the f the
first Trump administration.
Barry also
authored
project
2025's section on the Department of
Labor and other labor related agencies
which call for weakening federal minimum
wage, limiting overtime eligibility, and
undermining workers rights to a union by
forcing secret ballot elections. Now,
Jonathan
Barry is one of the authors who authored
the section on labor in project
2025. Now, how you do not know the
people who authored project
2025 and yet they are holding multiple
positions in the cabinet is just kind of
strange to me.
But be that as it
may, let's let's hear what Jonathan
Barry had to say in that section on the
Department of Labor
um that he wrote in Project 25 that he
authored in Project 2025. We're going to
go to the next
slide and uh I want y'all to listen.
This is an interview.
Jonathan uh Jonathan Barry is being
interviewed here and I want you to just
listen to what he has to say. Go ahead
and let's play
that on those issues. Yes, for sure. Um
but there there are implications for
social conservative values across many
issues. Uh, one of the interesting
proposals um that that you've laid out
in in project 2025 handbook from
heritage is uh stuff around the Sabbath.
What what are some of the ideas that you
have there? Yes. Um, so uh this is it
sounds it sounds controversial. Um uh in
many respects it is a it is a return to
something that basically always everyone
ever had. um uh and it it's specifically
the idea of um encouraging Sabbath rest
um through discouraging commerce um on
on the Sabbath. Um the the the proposal
that's in our book is uh amending the
the basic federal overtime law, Fair
Labor Standards Act to require that
overtime be paid uh for all work uh done
on the Sabbath. Um Oh, interesting. Yes.
Um, so I don't think um uh I don't think
I don't think Congress has um the
authority to mandate like a national
closing on on the Sabbath. This was that
was always a a state decision um to do
that. But I let me add it was always a
state decision to to do that. they
didn't. And and yeah, I'm not, you know,
I'm not saying this practice was
uniform, homogeneous, whatever, but um
very very widely spread and only only
recently in the last um few decades um
have uh have most states moved moved
away from this. Um so this is um I think
this is about as far as the federal
government could could properly go in
this space. Um but it would be an
encouragement and inducement um uh to um
to to rest really to kind of coordinate
commercial activity for the other six
days of of the week which is as for as
as long as we've had sabotarian uh
civilization you know beginning like
beginning in Israel and continuing into
Christendom. Um this is something that's
been increasingly a part of the rhythm
of civic life. uh most importantly for
people to have space to worship and
honor God. Um and and secondly to have
times of communal rest uh with their
families and with their communities. Do
you think in a in an America where
family formation has
plummeted, the commercialization of
every part of life is is is continuing
and abundant um and religious observance
is is down. Yes.
Do you think this would just result in
like people getting paid more on Sunday
and but but it would look all the same?
I So I think I think there would be some
of that like I I don't think this is a I
don't think this is a panacea. Um uh
it's but the law look the law is a real
teacher. Um I think this would I think
it would prompt as as all laws do um
meaningful reflection by by serious
numbers of people about um the
importance of rest and what what rest is
for uh and and separate and apart from
uh its hordatory function um it's it it
changes economic incentives and so I I
do think you would have a lot of
employers who would be shifting work a
lot of a lot of employers
do a fair amount of this already because
a lot of people naturally disfavor um
Sabbath work for what for whatever
reason and often command some kind of
premium um to uh to work on that.
Okay. So I want y'all to see
now as a church we have been we have
been saying
listen a Sunday law is not going to be
it's not going to be a secular Sunday
law.
The Sunday law is designed to bring
worship to God, the God of the
Bible, not the God of nature, not new
Aagism, not
secularism, a a
so-called green Sabbath being passed
just for the earth to to, you know, be
at rest. and and and atheists are like,
"Hey, I got I got the day off,
whatever." That's not what we're talking
about here in
prophecy. We already have a weekend.
People get Saturdays off, Sundays off.
We already have a weekend. That's not
what is being spoken of here. What is
being spoken of
here is worship of the Christian God.
That's the kind of Sunday law that's
going to be passed. Now, I've said this
time and time again. When we cry
wolf over everything, everything is a
Sunday law. This going to lead to Sunday
law and this going to lead to Sunday.
Then nothing leads to Sunday
law. And and we lose
credibility. Listen to me y'all. We lose
credibility when we continue to cry.
Wolf wolf wolf wolf wolf. Sunday law
Sunday. Sunday law. Sunday law. You
remember? Y'all remember a couple years
COP 26, COP 27. This was going to be it.
It was going to be a great Now listen
y'all. There was no need. There was
never any need for us to go anywhere
near there because prophecy already told
us this is what's going to happen. We
don't need to guess. We don't need to
conjecture. We don't We just sit back
and relax and wait and let it come. Now,
let me be clear to say y'all, and I'm
going to say, and you're going to be
like, "But pastor, you're saying what?"
Here's what I'm telling you.
Even though you heard what you just
heard, and even though Project 2025
includes this plan that you've just
heard Jonathan Barry say himself, nobody
putting it in his mouth, him saying it
himself, a Sunday law
still will be violently
opposed if they were to pass it.
Now, please understand what I'm saying.
you if you were quiet about Christian
nationalism before and now it's like,
"Oh, okay. Yeah, prophecy was exactly
what it said it was going to be." So now
I'm going to
start doing this, this, this, and this.
And you guys, we
must we must return to studying the
Bible. We cannot jump at everything
because when we jump at everything, we
lose credibility. And what I'm saying to
you now, beloved, is even though talk of
a Sunday law is now happening at the
highest levels of our
government. All that's happening right
now is God is showing us where their
minds
are. That's what he's doing. He's just
showing us, listen, I want you to see
they are thinking about this. Other
things need to happen. This is not yet
it. I'm not on here to say, "All right,
everybody, it's time to panic." What I'm
here to say is, can we
please return to a solid study of the
Bible and not jump
on the
bandwagons that take us away from what
we have always taught as prophecy?
I'm going to show you why this is so
important. Let's go back. I'm going to
show you one more video and then we're
going to do a little Bible study. A very
little Bible study. But y'all need to
see this because we need to talk about
shiny objects. Before we do that, I want
you to check out this next video.
Um and and then what are what are the
pitches? What are sort of like here's
you know I think you mentioned in your
article sort of like we need to
particularly post pandemic where all
lines between work and home have been
blurred and there's there's you know
sometimes I like working from home on
Friday if I can but general matter I
liked the days when we went into the
office because then we went home from
the office. Yes. and we were home, you
know. Um, so how do you so you pitch the
idea of maybe sort of, you know, having
more sort of
um, you know, rules around keeping the
Sabbath holy, right? Um, so what are
what are the I guess the big picture?
How do we sell America on this vision of
labor is good? Um and and and and sacred
and um and uh and also then what are we
how do we what what what are you on day
one take into the new Secretary of
Labor, you know? So my my I I I probably
my probably my biggest recommendation
here um to take to to go a step more
concrete than than work as service as
valuable as I think that is as the as
the overall frame is promoting um
promoting worker agency promoting worker
ownership. Um, these are and that's I
and I mean that in both the the formal
sense of of ownership and also the
colloquial sense of of ownership. Both
of which I know that lots of business
owners, you know, I'm I'm the I'm the
managing partner of a legal boutique.
I'm a small business owner and um the
level of of ownership and investment by
my by my employees matters a lot um to
to me and to the su success of our firm.
Um so one one very concrete and tangible
example of this is um Congress uh last
year I want to say um passed a a new law
to um facilitate encourage the formation
of ESOPS employee stock ownership plans
um or programs um which through uh Orisa
the main retirement uh benefits law um
has a there's a setting where you can
have you can reduce some of the inherent
asymmetries you have between uh an
employer and individual workers not into
collective bargaining though that that
has its legitimate role as well and then
you you alluded to this but uh something
that something I really encourage I
don't see a big it's harder to see a big
federal role for this I think this is
more a question of state and local law
is um reinvigorating where possible
Sabbath rest laws um that having as long
as you still buy beer on the Sabbath,
right? It's weird. Like what's what's
weird is the sort of the the sort of the
specifically
anti-alcohol either like either either
no business or all business, not just
like just anti-alcohol. It's it's a
little it's a little strange. I I think
if we trace some of the history there,
um I think I think you know the
Catholics might not like what they might
not like what they find. Um but um to be
very to be very specific like it used to
this was basically the norm through as
best I I've looked into this some
working on some research on this um
really going literally dating back to
Constantine um and his recognition of
Christianity in the Roman Empire that
you've had a pretty consistent tradition
in in Western civilization of of taking
like taking Sunday off uh from from
commerce. Um, this of course this is a
tradition that has roots not only in
Christianity but in in Judaism, right?
Um, and and keeping the Sabbath holy.
Um, and having a having a time not only
for it's not merely from rest in the
sense of of of abstinence from work, but
it's it's rest for it's rest for time
with God, time worshiping God. It's rest
for time with community or and even
before in between is time with family.
um the the lack one of the things that I
think has been so um so harmful to the
world of work and how we think about
work is the lack of of kind of
well-defined and shared times for rest.
Um one of the best uh pieces on this
from a a secular secular-ish author um
named uh Judith Schulvitz put this in
the Atlantic a few years ago called Why
You Never See Your Friends Anymore. Um
and she opens with talking about the
Soviet experiment in abolishing the
7-day uh week, replacing it with a
five-day week where just 1if of all the
people are randomly assigned like you
will have this day off, you will have
this day off. It was a debacle. Um and
within a few years even the Soviets had
to admit this was a very bad idea. like
the these are like you know these are
the masters of the even the goolog
people thought like thought that this
was a bad idea like we can't keep doing
this. Um so having that having more of
that steadier rhythm of work and rest
would be so much healthier so much
happier and help people more readily
connect with the purpose of their work.
Being able to push back from your work
allows you to more readily see it as
service to God, service to family,
service to community. um than the the
weird um kind of soup of half rest, half
work that we all seem to be floating in
all the time. That think like teleawwork
makes that harder to to to see um often
times. Um and um and likewise just the
ad the advent of like lots of
recreational internet use in the middle
of the workday. And
you may have heard him mention uh
telework
So meaning, hey, if you're working from
home, there's no real clear distinction
between work and rest. And I don't know,
but I suspect that part of this whole
y'all have to go back to work uh uh
thing that's
happening may have something to do with
that. Now, I don't know. That's just me
conjecturing, supposing. However, please
note what he just said because some
people when when project 202 2025 was
written and you know they were like well
this is not really a Sunday law cuz they
make mention of Sabbath and Sunday or
Saturday and Sunday. Please note what he
just said here. He just said listen in
Russia they were giving everybody the
days they wanted and it was this kind of
soupy just didn't work. It was a
debacle. So it's better to have shared
time together the same time together.
Remember you guys, it starts
mild. It starts mild, but it will get
progressively
worse. And what's crazy about this, you
guys, is that so
many I'll hold my thought. Let's go back
to the screen. I'm gonna come back to
this thought. Let's go back to the
screen. And this is
um this is an
article written just recently. Christian
nationalists and project 20 2025 had a
have a radical scheme to remake your
weekends.
Wow.
Wow. Let's keep moving. Next
slide. Americans United. So that's
that's the website is from Americans
United have been sounding the alarm
about project 2025, a radical Christian
nationalist blueprint to remake American
society along theoccratic
lines. Project 2025 is exactly what you
would expect from Christian
nationalists. It calls for restricting
reproductive freedoms and rolling back
LGBTQ rights. and it seeks to install an
extreme vision of religious freedom that
would enable people to use their faith
to ignore many civil rights and other
secular laws. But there's another
section that could affect every American
that should not be overlooked. The
architects of Project 2025 want to
control how you spend your
weekend. Come on, somebody. Let's keep
moving. Next slide.
A section on employment
policy written by Jonathan Bry, a member
of the Conservative Federalist Society,
would, if implemented, subject Americans
leisure time to government oversight by
limiting what you can do on Sundays. God
ordained the Sabbath as a day of rest.
And until very recently, the
Judeo-Christian tradition sought to
honor that mandate, that mandate, that
mandate by moral and legal regulation of
work on that day. Barry writes,
Elsewhere, he adds, unfortunately, that
communal day of rest has eroded under
the pressures of consumerism and
secularism.
So, do y'all see what's going on here?
this. I don't understand how we as
Adventists have argued, well, you don't
know where the Sunday law can come from.
Really, we don't know where the Sunday
law can come from. It could come from
secularists. Really, secularists are
going to say, "Hey guys, you need to
worship Jesus on Sunday." Secularists
are really going to do that.
what is so often called the godless
party is going to go ahead and seek to
implement worship of
Jesus through a Sunday
Sabbath. How did we get to the place
where we're now confused or we don't
know or can't say for sure what we have
always known for sure, which is that
apostate Christianity was going to
hijack politics in order to pass a
Sunday
law. How is it even possible for this
confusion to be going
on? Let me show you something. Let's go
back to the screen. I want you to see
this. Nationwide anti-Trump protest
planned for April 19th. What to know? Do
you all see that? Let me ask you a
question.
If if a Sunday law were passed
today, do you think that America would
be like, "Oh, well, there's a Sunday
law. We've now got to worship Jesus. All
right, everyone. Let's go. Put a one in
the chat if you think that they would do
that. Put a nine in the chat if you know
that they would not do
that. So, one in the chat if you
think Project 2025 a Sunday law gets
passed and now everybody is going to be
like, "All right, we're going to go
along with
this." Absolutely, Sherwin. People just
don't want to hear it.
It's kind of sad to me
that we've almost degraded prophecy
to to
sports. Your team is going to lose. No,
your team is going to lose. No, your
team Well, what about your What did your
team do? Wait a minute, y'all. We have
teams in this.
Why are we
defending
teams? Now, some people have said,
"Well, pastor, how come how come you
don't talk about the the wrongs that
that this group is
doing?" Which is almost like asking me,
"How come you don't talk about the the
evils of Islam?
It's not that I don't talk about these
things. It's that prophecy says yes, all
kinds of things are going to be
happening in the world. Yes, there will
be uh uh Islamic terrorists and yes, you
know, there will be X Y and Z and other
things happening. But I want you to
know that according to the
Bible, the main antagonist at the time
of the end will be a religial political
power. Keep your eyes locked on that.
And yet for so many of us, we're
treating this religial political power
as this as if it's our team. Well, how
do you know it's going to be this
religio political power? It could
be. I need y'all to see
this. Selected messages volume 3, page
428 says this. They
declared that they had the truth. Next
slide. They declared that they had the
truth. That miracles were among them.
That angels from heaven talked with them
and walked with them. That great power
and signs and wonders were performed
among them. And that this was the
temporal
millennium they had been expecting so
long. The whole world was
converted and in harmony with the Sunday
law. Stop for a
second. Come back. Let's Let's What does
it mean that the whole world was
converted? If the whole world is
converted, are there still
Muslims who don't believe that Jesus is
is
God? Are there still
atheists? Are there still
secularists? Are there are there still
newagers? No. No. No. No, no, no,
no. All of those things
cease because
everybody, the whole world is converted.
So now the simple question is what is it
that converts the whole world? Well,
here's what we do know from this quote
that at this time the whole world is
saying this is the long awaited
millennium. Well, what does a Christian
world think the millennium is?
The Christian world believes that the
millennium is when Jesus has come and
sets up a thousand years of peace on the
earth. And they cannot believe that the
millennium begins without Jesus being
here. Are y'all following
me? If the people at this time, if the
whole world is converted and everybody's
saying this is the one, this is the
10,000 years, the millennium, it must be
that something supernatural happened.
And that supernatural
thing is the
coming of
Jesus. But it's not
Jesus. Y'all understand now that even if
Project 2025 succeeded in attempting to
pass a Sunday law that it would only
cause more rebellion, it would only
cause a a a rebellion and uprising,
marches, protests. But that's not what
Revelation says. Revelation doesn't say
there going to be protests from all
different kinds of Revelation says that
the whole world will be united against a
small group. Come on, let's go back to
the
screen. The whole world was converted
and in harmony with the Sunday law. And
this little feeble people stood out in
defiance of the laws of the land. Not
atheists, not the LGBTQ
community, not the Marxists, not the
communists. A little feeble people stood
out in defiance of the law, which means
everybody else is on board. Here's why
I'm telling y'all this, y'all.
Because if the Sunday law is not passed,
for some of y'all in the next four
years, you're going to be
like, and we don't need to have that
position. We don't need to say the
Sunday law is going to be passed in the
next four years. That shouldn't be
coming out of our
mouths because prophetically speaking,
there is
nothing that anyone can do to convert
the whole world
except a supernatural miracle.
And beloved, when that miracle happens,
there's no
warning. That's why all 10 virgins are
sleeping when midnight
strikes. It's not something that you can
see coming down the
road. Beloved, what I'm telling you is
this. Yes. Project 25 2025 is
significant. But you know what you're
gonna see? You're gonna see a whole
bunch of people who weren't talking
about it before who are now like, "Okay,
well, I better start talking about it
now." And I'm going to go to the other
extreme of, "Yep, it's coming. Sunday
law is about to pass in the next two
months, in the next three months." And
listen, y'all, the there's a reason I'm
pointing there's a reason why it is so
important for us to be balanced when it
comes to prophecy, y'all.
Let's talk about shiny objects and then
we're going to wrap this up. How many of
you know what shiny object syndrome is?
Put a one in the chat if you know what
shiny object syndrome is. One in the
chat. Shiny object
syndrome. All right, let me go to the
screen.
Um, shiny objects.
Shiny object syndrome is the inclination
to be quickly
sidetracked by fresh and thrilling
possibilities frequently resulting
uh in the abandonment of ongoing tasks
or
objectives causing a reduction in
productivity and hindering advancement
towards long-term goals, missions, etc.
Shiny object syndrome. It's a phenomenon
where individuals or businesses get
caught up in the allure of new ideas,
projects, or opportunities, neglecting
or abandoning ongoing efforts. Let's go
to the next slide. Causes. What causes
shiny object syndrome? A fear of missing
out. The constant pursuit of new things
can stem from a fear of missing out on
potential opportunities. Lack of focus.
Shiny object syndrome can indicate
difficulty in staying focused on a
single task or project. Surface level
attract surface level attractiveness.
People may be drawn to the shininess or
perceived value of new ideas without
fully evaluating their practicality or
long-term viability. I want to suggest
to you y'all. I want to suggest to
you that many of us have shiny object
syndrome. We do not know how to stay
focused on what prophecy says. So,
anything that comes up that seems like
it can be a crisis or seems like it can
be a time of trouble or seems like this
could lead to the mark of the beast, we
are off on it. Yes. I'm going to be a
martyr for this. And we get
distracted by shiny
objects. And as we're being distracted
from shiny objects, we're quiet on the
thing that matters the
most. Our church right
now is in
turmoil while the devil is on a
march. We're in turmoil right now. Inner
turmoil. talk talks about splitting the
church and and and leadership and this
and that and and and you know the church
is now Babylon because uh they don't
believe in in uh they believe in the
trinity and and all kinds of shiny
objects, climate change, The Pope said
this over here.
It's amazing to me how I'm hearing
people
talk people talking about everything
else that's going on around the the
globe and in Rome and here and there and
there but very
little very few
people were talking about the were
warning about Christian nationalism and
what was coming.
It was almost like it was
taboo to say anything about Christian
nationalism. And if you said something
about Christian nationalism, you were
just I don't know
woke. Let's go back to consequences.
Let's go back to the screen. So what are
the consequences of un of a of a shiny
object shiny object syndrome?
Individuals or business may start
numerous projects but fail to complete
them leading to a backlog of unfinished
work. Unfinished work. Reduce
productivity. Constant switching between
task and projects can significantly
hinder productivity and progress. Missed
opportunities. By constantly chasing
after rabbits, I mean new ideas,
individuals or businesses may miss out
on opportunities to build up their
current strength and develop existing
projects. Do you think that Satan would
love to have us miss out on
opportunities? What do y'all think? What
do you all
think? If there is anyone, any voice
that should have been heard the loudest
warning against what project 2025 was
proposing and the hijacking of a
Christian movement. uh the the Christian
movement hijacking a particular
political
brand. That voice should have been the
voice of Adventists. But no, no, no, no,
no, no.
Instead, we were busy.
I want to say we were busy, but I need
to say we are
busy still chasing after shiny
objects. The devil has let loose so many
cute
bunnies. Distraction
bunnies. We're about to wrap this up.
We're about to wrap this up.
Um, so what is the what is the silver
object? The shiny silver
thing. I'm going to give you a story
from the Old Testament. Let's go. Do
y'all recognize this
picture? It's not the actual picture,
but what is this? What is this about?
What is this
about? Uh uh Queen, please note, I hear
you. Please note, I'm not
criticizing the church. That's not what
I'm doing. What I'm talking about, what
I'm doing, what I'm what I'm addressing
here is a
very
unfortunately
already
very dangerous
position that members of the church are
in. So, we're not talking about X, Y,
and Z. We're talking about people in the
church that are being distracted by
shiny
objects. I hope you get that. So, what
picture did y'all just see? This is not
an actual picture of the thing, but it
is a picture of the golden calf. Shiny
objects. I want you to check this out,
y'all. In Exodus 32:1, listen to what
the Bible says. And when the people saw
that Moses delayed to come down out of
the mount, the people gathered
themselves together unto Aaron, and said
unto him, "Up, make us gods, which shall
go before us. For as for this, Moses,
the man that brought us up out of the
land of Egypt, we want not what is
become of him." And Aaron said unto
them, "Break off the golden earrings,
which are in your in the ears of your
wives, and your sons, and your
daughters, and bring them unto me." And
all the people break off the golden
earrings which were in their ears and
brought them unto Aaron. And Aaron
received them at their hand and
fashioned it with a graving tool after
he had made it a molten calf. And they
said, "These be thy gods, O Israel,
which brought thee up out of the land of
Egypt." And when Aaron saw it, he built
an altar before it. And Aaron made
proclamation and said, "Tomorrow is the
feast of the Lord." And they rose up
early on the tomorrow and offered burnt
offerings and brought peace offerings.
And the people sat down to eat and to
drink and rose up to play. Now, I need
to break this story down just for a few
moments longer and then we're done.
Listen to me,
y'all.
Moses had gone
away. And now in the minds of the
people, in the minds of the people, he's
taking too long to come
back. In the minds of the people, Sunday
law is taking too long to happen. In the
minds of the people, prophecy is taking
too long to happen. Is it going to
happen the way we were we were
told? Is the prophecy sure? Is it
certain? Are things the way is it going
to happen this
way? And so when Moses doesn't return
when they expect, what do they
do? They the people clamor for a new
God. They they want a shiny
object. I hope y'all are catching
this. They needed something. And watch
this now. Aaron who was the priest.
Aaron who was the leader. Listen to me
y'all. We have a lot of
Aarons who are giving the people who
want shiny
objects. Aaron was this type of person.
Well, okay. So, what do the people want?
All right. I'll give them what they
want. I'll give them what they
want. Beloved, God forbid that we as
ministers, that we as preachers, that we
as ministries, that we as independent
ministries be like Aaron in giving the
people what they want because there's a
delay. And oh, what are the people
clamoring for? All right. Well, I'mma
jump on this because that's what the
people want. That's what I'm going to
give them. And we are creating golden
calves of prophecy. We are creating
golden calves that are redirecting the
minds of the
people at a time when the people are
clamoring because they want to know
what's going on. You know, things are
taking so what's going on. The last
thing we should be doing is creating
golden
calves, creating shiny images to say,
"Come on, people. Let's get worked up
over this. Come on." And and watch what
Aaron did. Aaron said, "This is a feast
unto the
Lord." This is a feast unto the Lord.
Aaron was after clicks and views.
Aaron, we like
you. We like
you. You're telling us what we want to
hear. You're telling us what we want to
hear.
God
forbid that we as ministers and
preachers stay
silent or curb what needs to be
said because we want to please people.
It's interesting that there was a golden
calf. It's interesting that it was a
golden calf that the people started
worshiping. Let's go to the last
slide. Um, what is the golden calf in
the last days?
What is the golden calf in the last
days?
Yeah, it's another beast with
horns, horns like a
lamb that speak like a
dragon. Could it be possible, beloved,
that many Adventists have been so caught
up in the shiny
thing that the golden calf for us
now, the golden calf that has entered
into the midst of the
church is apostate Protestantism.
is that movement that has merged
Christianity with politics and says if
you're a true Christian this is what you
believe and if you're a true Christian
this is what you stand against and if
you're a true Christian then this is how
you should this be the these be thy
gods could it be that the shiny
object that seems to now be controlling
whatever is said on certain platform
forms and whatever is believed in
certain circles now finds it way its way
into Adventism. And I'm going to tell
you something, the populist
movement, the populist
movement in which the view that the
government is
evil. And that's so strange y'all
because in prophecy it's not the
government that's evil. It's Christians
who hijack the government that's
evil. That's what prophecy says. But
here we have a movement saying the
government is evil and unless we take
over the government, we are all going to
be doomed.
And that spirit of overthrowing the
leadership and overthrowing and draining
the swamp. Could is it possible that
that same spirit that is running a muck
in Christian nationalism has now entered
into the
church to now where it is a it is a pat
on the back to be like, "Yeah, man. The
leadership of our church, we need to
drain the
swamp. The leaders of our church, they
are wicked. They It's cruel now. It's
You want You want You want
um uh virtue
signaling. Call the Call the leadership
of the church evil. Call the leadership
of the church Babylon. Compare the
leadership of the church to the papacy
or the pope, the wicked. Just do that
and you'll be like, "Oh, you're present
truth. Wow." Yeah, man. You're present
truth. Beloved, understand that ex the
exact
spirit which now says, "I have no
respect for the leadership of the
government." Remember what Paul said?
Paul said the government was ordained of
God. Not that the government is godly,
but the government is ordained of God.
So this idea of they're crooked and they
may be and God still says obey the
government as long as they do not cross
uh uh or or tell you to go against my
will. First four
commandments. And now the same
spirit in in this religion political
power that seeks to put distrust in the
government and don't trust and they're
lying and they're this and they're that.
That same spirit has now entered the
golden calf has now entered into
Adventism. There were one people
There was it was the
Levites while everybody else was going
on this frenzy of forget about
Moses and worshiping the golden. There
was one people, one tribe, the Levites,
who are like,
"Yeah, we're not done with
this. Nope. We're not down against this
rebel. We're not done with this
rebellion. We're not down with this. You
know, we're going to we're going to go a
new route. we're going to we're going to
believe a new way. Nope, we're not down
with
that. And my appeal to you is this,
guys, because it's getting to the place
now where appeals are just falling on
deaf ears. So for those that have ears
to
hear, for those that have ears to
hear, stay the course, y'all.
Stay the
course. Get into your
word. No one's saying put trust in the
GC. No one's saying put trust in men.
Nobody said that. Pastor Myers didn't
say that. That didn't come out my mouth.
Listen. Listen carefully.
No one is saying to what I am
saying is that the devil is the master
of mental
manipulation to the point where he got a
third of the angels to distrust God
himself.
So if at the end of time we know that
the dragon is the one attacking the
woman attacking the church, then it
would behoove us not to be a part of any
movement that attacks the
church. I didn't say that. Ellen White
said
that. And listen y'all. Even the bearing
of false
witness. Even the bearing of false
witness. Some of us need to be very
careful
y'all. Pastor Myers said this. Pastor
Myers said that. Pastor Myers call this
this one or this one that. Listen y'all.
The bearing of fault. We heard Jesus
say, "Destroy this temple and and he
will build it again in." We heard him
say with our own ears. We heard him.
Listen. The devil is a master
manipulator and his whole goal is to
cause us to turn our weapons on one
another.
It's it's very sad you
guys. Some some of us are going to come
to the real to the realization of how
deceived and led
astray we were because we refuse to have
our hearts
softened by the Holy Spirit.
When
Moses, when Naab and
Abaiu, when
Kora and his people were killed, you
know what the people said? After God
destroyed them, they turned around and
said, "You have killed the people of the
Lord."
The time is coming where if it were
possible, even the very elect would be
deceived. And I'm just going to say this
and I'm going to close y'all. If your
heart is not right with
God, it will be easy for the devil to
deceive
you. It'll be
easy. It will be
easy. My
appeal. My appeal, you guys.
is tested by the
word. Get back into the
Bible. Stop chasing shiny
objects. Yes, Nicole. Babylon has some
strong
wine. And I think it only takes a sip,
y'all. It only takes a
sip to have you totally
drunk. All
right, that's
it. I
am I'm
done.
Um, please study you guys. Please
study
things. Prophecy is unfolding before our
eyes. And the one thing the devil wants
more than
anything is for the church to
disintegrate, to f to to
become to just be
divided. All right. Heavenly
Father, Lord, thwart the enemy's
plans. Lord, help us to stop chasing
shiny
objects and stay
committed to what you have spoken
through the word and through your
prophet. Lord, remove every new version
of prophecy. Remove the idea that that
that the Sunday law could come from
anywhere and from anybody. Lord, help us
to remember what the prophecy actually
says.
And Lord, remove the spirit of
antagonism. Remove this
populist uprising that is happening in
our church, in our midst, under a
disguise of righteousness. Remove it,
Lord. Expose it for what it is. It is
coming from many different corners, many
different factions saying, "The church
is Babylon because of this. The church
is Babylon because they no longer
believe this. The church is Babylon
because X Y andZ. Lord, remove that.
There is a Leodysian message. But that
is not it. It is not that the church is
Babylon. It is not that the church is
fallen. It is not that the church has
become like the papacy. It is none of
those things.
Lord, the real issue is our heart
issue. We are we are not loving people.
We're not loving one another.
We have lamps without
oil. Lord,
please open the eyes of your people.
Open the eyes of those even now
steeped in this
deception. Wake us up,
Lord, because the time is near.
Thank you Lord for hearing and for
answering. We pray this in Jesus name.
Amen. All right y'all.
Um thank you for uh for tuning
in. Um I am
uh y'all haven't seen me on, you know,
Power of the Lamb in a little while
because I've been going, you know,
through the loss of my brother and
dealing with that. And um I'm going to
be on more often and we're going to be
dealing with these issues more often. So
just know you're like, "Where's Pastor
Myers been?" Just know uh I am not
silent. I will not be
silent. Um so y'all pray for me and pray
for our church and pray y'all that we
get back on
track in Jesus name.
Amen. Uh if you don't follow the
channel, make sure you subscribe. As I
go live, you'll get notifications. So,
make sure you do that. And again, may
God bless you and may God keep you.